

Profile

Highly motivated and academically accomplished student with a strong commitment to learning and contributing to the advancement of knowledge in the field. Distinctive skills are: diligence, perseverance, curiosity, sociability. I have experience working with the following technology stack: C/C++, Python, Java, Qt, Android development.

Employment Experience

Resident of the IT-Academy at "HEЙMAPK", Nizhniy Novgorod 2022 — Present

Work with talented young people in Russia, helping to solve cases of leading companies in practice. Over the course of several days, participants solve cases such as: olympiad programming, application development. One of my team won in the last category, having implemented with my support an application for analyzing the amount of lactate in the blood with a graph of the dependence of lactic acid salts in the blood on the time of exercise: click.

Private tutor for the Unified State Exam, Nizhniy Novgorod

2022 — Present

Prepare high school students (grades 10-11) for the Unified State Exam in specialized mathematics and computer science. Prepared more than 18 students. Topics covered were: interpolation, systems of nonlinear equations, convex polygons and their intersection areas, algorithms, data structures.

Pet projects:

- Smart voice assistant for the driver (Flet, Python, Pandas): click
- Intersection area calculator for convex polygons (Qt, C++): click
- Mobile messenger application (Android, Firebase, Java): click
- Interpolation with cubic splines (Gnuplot, C): click

Education

Technical Lyceum #38, Nizhniy Novgorod

2019 - 2022

HSE University, Nizhniy Novgorod

2022 — Present

Applied Mathematics and Information Science

Courses

Samsung IT-School, Mobile development

2019 - 2020

Details

Nizhniy Novgorod Russian Federation +79308106722 pddMas@mail.ru

Date of birth 10.11.2003

Links

GitHub Telegram VK

Skills

Communication

Creativity

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Time Management

Teamwork

Languages

Russian

English

Hobbies

- Application development
- Tutoring (maths and informatics, Unified State Exam)
- Mathematics
- Squash and judo